A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., No. 6 Mine, Outside Operating Facilities, Newhall, West Virginia, No Mine Workings, 1964/08/18 (Box 436)
  - Consolidation Coal Co., Matthews Mine, Location No. 1 Surface Layout, No mine workings, 1979/05/25 (Box 436)
  - Lower Mine #2 North Main, Slope Profile, no mine workings (Box 436)
  - Consolidation Coal Company, Matthews Mine 3 Mine Slope Bottom, Plan and Elevation Map, No mine workings, 1975/08/29 (Box 437)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Tracks and Virginia Railway Profiles, no mine workings (Box 437)
  - No mine workings, unknown profiles (Box 438)
  - Railroad tracks along side the Guyandotte River, Kepler mine area, Norfolk and Western Railway System (Box 438)
  - Proposed mine area for Kepler mine, no real mine area (Box 438)
  - No mine workings, topographic map showing possible holdings and borehole locations (Box 438)
  - Drill hole info, Big Huff Coal Co., no mine workings (Box 438)
  - Moco Cleaning Plant, Dry Cleaning Schematic (Box 439)
  - No mine workings, Proposed Addition to Pocahontas Cemetery (Box 439)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Matthews #1 Mine, Outside supply yardmap, no mine workings, 1974/11/25 (Box 440)
  - No mine workings, topographic map showing possible cropline in Mercer County (Box 440)
  - Graph showing cross section (Box 440)
  - Property outlines of/within the Itmann leasehold and Guyandotte leasehold for different coal companies, No. 9 seam, Eureka property (Box 440)
  - Virginia Limestone Corp., proposed water tank, no mine workings, 1966 (Box 441)
  - West Virginia Stone Coal Branch, Killarney, Raleigh County, West Virginia (Box 441)
  - Bishop Sand Dryer, #34 (Box 441)
  - No mine workings, map showing lots desired by Nick Crist from N&W Railroad Co., Pocahontas, Virginia (Box 441)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., wash house and main office plans, Pocahontas, Virginia, 1932 (Box 442)
  - Consolidation Coal Co., Matthews Mine 3, mine slope bottom, Evacuation and support plan, no mine workings, 1975/09/12 (Box 442)
  - Consolidation Coal Co., Matthews Mine, Location No. 2, surface layout, no mine workings, 1979/05/24 (Box 442)
  - No mine workings, 3-C Haul road Upper Bench, 1980/05/15 (Box 442)
  - No mine workings, map showing portions of Pocahontas, Virginia and Bluestone Junction, West Virginia (Box 442)
  - No mine workings, Profile of Haul Road, 1977 (Box 443)
  - No mine workings, Map showing Town of Pocahontas including routes, streets, and creeks, Tazewell County, Virginia, 1968/03/19 (Box 443)
  - Consolidation Coal Company, Page Preparation Plant, no mine workings, 1970/07/22 (Box 443)
  - Buckeye Augering Estimate location map, Fire Creek seam area #1, no mine workings (Box 443)
  - Kepler mine site plan, map of area including surface features, no mine workings (Box 443)
  - Profile of Nos. 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10, 11 and Sewell seams, no mine workings (Box 443)
  - No mine workings, Old original track layout near Wallace Cabin Branch of Guyandotte River (Box 443)
  - No mine workings, G&A Coal Co., G&A No. 2 mine, BH39, Cross Section (Box 443)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Crane Creek Tipple Water, no mine workings, 1971/02/23 (Box 444)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Crane Creek No. 11, no mine workings, 1971/02/24 (Box 444)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Elkhorn No. 11 mine, water system, no mine workings, 1971/03/08 (Box 444)
  - topographic map for the Consol and on Virginia/West Virginia border - McDowell and Tazewell County, no mine works (Box 444)
  - Right of way and track map, Virginian and Western Railway Company, Guyandotte River line, no mine workings, 1930 (Box 445)
  - No mine workings, Consolidation Coal Co., Bishop Mountain Top, #58, 96, and 9 seams crop, 1979/02/20 (Box 445)
  - Boreholes, no mine workings (Box 445)
  - No mine workings, No. 13 Seam crop line, Crane Creek (Box 445)
  - No mine workings, Doctor's office and residence plans, 1934 (Box 446)
  - No mine workings, Borehole location, No. 1 seam, 1963/06 (Box 446)
  - Seam outcrop outlines, Coal companies property outlines, Gas well locations (Box 446)
  - No mine workings, Bishop Lamp House, views & floor plans (Box 447)
  - X-section of emergency pond at Bishop Prep Plant, non coal mine workings (Box 447)
  - Data sheets (Box 448)
  - No mine workings, Itmann Coal Co., Profile of still run haulage road (Box 448)
  - Unknown mine, profile slope of bottom, no mine workings (Box 448)
  - Berwind Land Company, Seam sections, Pocahontas No. 3 seam, Borehole data, Wyoming County, West Virginia, 1943/08 (Box 449)
  - Consolidation Coal Co., Matthews Mine, Location - No. 3 Surface layout, 1979/05/25 (Box 449)
  - Pulaski Iron Co, Net tons per year for mines in Virginia and West Virginia, ca. 1930s-1970s (Box 450)
  - Virginia Carolina Coal Co., Oakwood, Virginia, Mine No. 1, Flat Rock Hollow, Russell County, Virginia, Widow Kennedy seam (Box 450)
  - Wakena Coal Company Inc., successors to Garden Coal Co., Drill, Virginia, No. 3 mine, Upper Banner seam (Box 450)
  - Partial Patrick County, Virginia map (Box 450)
  - Map of Pocahontas Coal Field, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Property (Box 451)
  - topographic map of Pocahontas Coal Field region with numbered areas, probably seams/mine sites (Box 452)
  - 115. Annual Tonnage Report, 1967 (Box 453)
  - Kanawha, New River, Logan, & Mineo Coal Fields (Two copies), 19-37 (Box 453)
  - Map of Buckhorn Iron and Improvement Company (Box 453)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. spreadsheets for mines, including names of superintendents, net tons, nearest towns, residences information, etc., 1952-1953 (Box 454)
  - 112. Tracings Annual Reports, 1958 thru 19-- (Box 454)
  - 246. Tracings, Annual Meeting, 1958/06-1959 (Box 455)
  - E-502 Map of Southern West Virginia and Northeastern Kentucky Coal Fields (Box 455)
  - E-502 Hanna Coal Co., Cleveland, Ohio, Map of Southern West Virginia and Northeastern Kentucky coal fields (Box 455)
  - 259. President's Meeting, 1967/07/26 (Box 456)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, Itmann Coal Flow Sheet, 1959/08/17 (Box 457)
    [Removed from map case drawer with no title.]
  - Piping plans (Box 457)
  - P- Bridge (Baby Mine), Bi- Bridge, Concrete, #37 Bridge, #37 Bridge (Tower Sec.), #37 Bridge (Bent Sec.), #37 Bridge (Girder Sec.), #37 Bridge (Girder Sec.), #37 Bridge (Foundation), #37 Bridge (Girder Sec.), #37 Bridge, #37 Bridge Girder Sec. (Box 457)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, Deerfield Mine, Proposed Slurry Disposal, 1956/02/23 (Box 458)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Itmann and Deerfield – Work Under Construction".]
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, Itmann Water Distribution, 1959/08/19 (Box 458)
  - Deerfield Shaft (Box 458)
  - Indian Creek Mine plans, 1944 (Box 458)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Misc."]
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. charts about mine sites, 1952 (Box 458)
  - topographic maps for Monterrey, Virginia-West Virginia, Staunton, Virginia-West Virginia, Rockbridge, Virginia-West Virginia, Flattop, Virginia-West Virginia Pounding Mill Quadrangle (Box 458)
  - 200. Tracings Annual Report, 1963 (Box 459)
  - Seam height (Box 460)
  - Aerial photographs of Kepler mine and unidentified areas [possibly Boissevain] (Box 460)
  - Aerial photographs [possibly of Boissevain or Kepler] (Box 461)
  - OSM #700138, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 7 maps of Itmann, Sugar Run, and other/unidentified areas (Box 462)
    Includes CON1032-1036
  - Itmann outcrops, no mine workings, map shows numerous seam outcrops (Box 463)
  - Topographic map of boreholes, Kentucky-Virginia border (Sagamore) (Box 463)
  - Maps of Raleigh, Mercer, and Wyoming counties (Box 463)
  - topographic maps of Mingo, Manring, Louisville Creek, etc. (Box 464)
  - Maitland no. 3 and 4 mine profiles (Box 465)
  - Geologic column, Greasy Creek shaft (Box 465)
  - Property lines for coal companies (Box 465)
  - Killarney-Lillybrook Coal Co., surface features, buildings, and building structures (Box 465)
  - Tennessee topographic map, Clinch - Powell Rivers Watershed (Box 465)
  - Map showing results of prospecting on 1728 acre tract owned by Big Hoff Coal Co., located at Big Huff Creek, Wyoming, West Virginia (Box 465)
  - Houses and roads, Pulaski Colliery, map #2, no mine workings (Box 466)
  - Map showing rivers and lease properties, no names for features (Box 466)
  - Aerial maps of Beckley Seam, Sewell Seam, #6 Seam (Box 466)
  - TN division, lands leased and owned (Box 466)
  - Map showing land of Rowland Company to be Included in sublease by Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. to Bruns Coal Company Inc., 1957/12 (Box 467)
  - Setter mine area (Box 467)
  - topographic and property maps, Consol Coal Co., Eckman-Page mine area (Box 467)
  - Shuttle Car turning radius drawings (Box 467)
  - Amigo topographic maps (Box 468)
  - Itmann Bridge plan details (Box 468)
  - [Algana Seam 13, Roser, Ann, Butch, Harry, Note Drame 3422?] (Box 468)
  - McDowell and Tazewell counties test holes; map of Berwind leasehold (Box 469)
  - topographic map of Consol lands - Russell County project, lower castle seam, lease property map (Box 469)
  - Geologic column, Johnny Branch air shaft (Box 469)
  - USGS maps for McGraws, Mullens, Matheny, and Pineville quadrangles in West Virginia, possibly mine location data and adit locations, no workings (Box 469)
  - Prospecting maps, Itmann property, upper seams, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 470)
  - No mine workings, Cumberland Plateau planning district, Buchanan, Dickenson, Russell, and Tazewell counties, Virginia, topographic map, roads and highways, probably original mineable extent of the bituminous coal seam in West Virginia, West Virginia geological and economic survey, maps of West Virginia, 1970 (Box 471)
  - Kepler mine slope profiles, no mine workings, 1967/07/26 (Box 471)
  - Rowland Land Co., Bottom Bench of Eagle Seam, Dorothy Coal Seam, and Coal sections, Raleigh County, West Virginia, 1946-1956 (Box 471)
  - Main shop building at Amonate (Box 471)
  - Store building for the Pocahontas Consolidated Collieries Co., Inc., to be built at JenkinJones, West Virginia (Box 471)
  - Beckley and Sewell seam maps, 1961 (Box 472)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., annual reports (Box 472)
  - Estimate Recoverable Reserves Remaining in the Pocahontas Low Volatile Coking Coal Field, 1961/12/31 (Box 473)
  - Disturbed Amonate Area, Consol, Amonate Quad (Box 473)
  - Itmann mine (Box 473)
  - USGS maps, Keen Mountain, Virginia and Patterson, Virginia-West Virginia quadrangle, 1977 (Box 474)
  - Red Oak Mountain, Consol Coal Co., topographic quadrangle maps, Campbell and Roane counties, Tennessee (Box 474)
  - Itmann Cabin Creek upper seams (Box 474)
  - Bishop Coal Co. (Box 474)
  - N&W Right of Way, Right Fork of Beech Fork, 1924 (Box 475)
  - Map showing outside facilities of Eckman No. 11 mine (Box 475)
  - Random boreholes (Box 475)
  - Beckley and Fire Creek seams (Box 475)
  - Itmann Mines, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Building and machinery plans, 1951 (Box 476)
  - Bristol Steel and Iron Works Inc. for Consolidation Coal Co., Refuse Conveyor Extension project, 1979/06-1979/07 (Box 476)
  - Unknown mines, accident reports (Box 476)
  - Turkey Gap section, Gregg Dixon (Box 476)
  - OSM #700472, Kentucky Block Fuel Co., Plat Showing Mine Town and Other Structures at Mine No. 2 - Ellwood, Pike County, Kentucky, blueprint, 1918/12/23 (Box 477)
    Identical to CON2690
  - Boissevain [aerial photographs] (Box 478)
  - Aerial photographs [possibly of Boissevain or Kepler] (Box 479)
  - Mine Map No. 1 of the Loup Creek Colliery Co., Page, West Virginia (Box 480)
  - Mine Map of the Twin Branch Mining Co., McDowell County, West Virginia (Box 480)
  - Angle, Booth-Bowen, No. 17 Turkey Gap Tract Fee, PLD-1485.03 (Box 480)
  - topographic map of West Virginia, including Bluefield, Three Forks, Rockhouse, Eckman-Page, and Shawnee (Box 480)
  - Charles H. Burchard, 412 East 83 Street, Analytique 1 - A Georgian Doorway (Box 481)
    Fragile!
  - Geological Cross-Section Showing Correlation of Lower Lee Coals, Pocahontas No. 3 Seam [negatives] (Box 482)
  - Aerial photographs [possibly of Boissevain or Kepler] (Box 482)
  - Assorted maps: Pocahontas Rail Lines and Stations from which Coal Rates Apply; Industrial Map Showing Present Development of the Smokeless Coal Fields of West Virginia, 1951-1952; Recoverable Reserves Feasibly Mineable Today, [1960?]; Vertical Sections, Principal Coal Seams; Mississippian 'Red Shale' [lists different mines and coals], 1951-1952, 1960 (Box 483)
  - OSM #700753 Peerless, #1 Mine (Box 483)
  - Map of Pocahontas, Virginia, and Big Vein Property Line (Box 483)
  - Four color coded maps of the Pocahontas Coal Field (Box 483)
  - Mine Map, B1 [unidentified mine and location] (Box 483)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. forecast and performance charts, 1957-1964 (Box 484)
  - Itmann Flow Chart (Box 484)
  - Principal coal burning electric power plants, east and midwest (Box 484)
  - topographic map, McDowell and Tazewell counties, Virginia and West Virginia (Box 484)
  - Map Showing Option Lands of Pocahontas Land Corporation by Kentland-Elkhorn Coal Corp. Situated in Martin, Pike, and Floyd Counties, KY, 1967/11 (Box 485)
  - Anderson, Campbell, Scott counties, Tennessee, coal leases, 1933, 1959 (Box 485)
  - Dry cleaning blueprint (Box 485)
  - Map showing cross section of Consol Bishop mine #34, Pocahontas 3 Seam, B-B' cross section (Box 485)
  - OSM #700270 Data sheets (Box 485)
  - Consolidated Coal Co., Pocahontas #3 Seam, mine plan, no mine workings, 1987/09 (Box 486)
  - USGS Beverly and Helton Quadrangle, Kentucky (Box 486)
  - Profile Fault Line, Jacobs Fork #2 (36 Mine) (Box 486)
  - [Unidentified map with elevations and mine entrances] (Box 486)
  - 180. Maitland conveyor plans (Box 487)
  - Faraday Upper Seaboard Seam (Box 487)
  - 236. BU-34 Buchanan Co. Railroad - Details, Buchanan and Tazewell Counties, old prints, Coal companies land property-lease boundaries near Clinch River, Red Ash Coal Company mine lands (Box 488)
  - County and mine maps, Pocahontas Coal Field (Box 488)
  - topographic maps showing different seams in Matthews mine area (Box 489)
  - Cabin Creek information (Box 489)
  - Map of West Virginia - showing coal, oil, gas, iron ore and limestone areas (Box 490)
  - Bishop Tipple, No. 33 Tracks (Box 491)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. map showing proposed surface layout of new mine on Ritter lease (Box 491)
  - Map of Breathitt, Knott, Floyd, and Magoffin counties, Kentucky, for Matewan Minerals Inc. (Box 491)
  - USGS map of Amonate Quadrangle, Virginia and West Virginia (Box 491)
  - Profiles of Jellico Seam for Consolidation Coal Co. (Box 491)
  - Consol Coal Co., cross section, Dry Fork, 9L seam structure (Box 492)
  - N&W Right of Way, Guyandotte River (Box 492)
  - USGS maps of quadrangles in Tennessee and Kentucky and highway map for Mercer County, West Virginia (Box 493)
  - West Virginia State Highway, right of way maps and plans (Box 493)
  - Topographical maps - different areas in West Virginia - Kimball, Carswell, and Vivian, West Virginia (Box 494)
  - Consolidation Coal Company, Amonate plant plans (Box 494)
  - Twin Falls State Park, West Virginia roads (Box 495)
  - Property maps for Ridge Land Co. (Box 496)
  - National Coal Association map of US, "Minimum Price Areas and Production Districts as Set Forth in the Bituminous Coal Act of 1937", 1937 (Box 497)
  - Itmann track and Virginian RR (Box 497)
  - Whittaker Ridge topographic map (Box 497)
  - West Mine Rock Dump (Box 497)
  - Crane Creek, #6 Seam, 1961/07/26 (Box 498)
  - Winding Gulf Coals Inc. property maps and tables, Goodwill, West Virginia (Box 498)
  - McCabe property and Kanawha River area maps, West Virginia (Box 498)
  - Berwind Land - Consol Lawsuit, Map of Three Forks, extra copies - to be used when the second copy gets lost, no mine workings (Box 499)
  - Electrical gridwork (Box 499)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bishop Coal Co., preparation plant - flowsheet (Box 499)
  - Crozer Coal & Land, Lynco, West Virginia (Box 499)
  - TN Railroad Co. surveys (Box 499)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Company, electrical lines (Box 500)
  - Piney Coking Land Company - land/property maps, Raleigh Co., West Virginia (Box 500)
  - OSM #700236 topographic profile (Box 501)
  - Mineable Seams Southern Division (Box 501)
  - Match #3-7 topographic maps (Box 501)
  - Lillybrook Coal Company's lease lines along Pines Creek & Stare Coal Creek (Box 502)
  - Data sheets (Box 502)
  - Four topographic maps of quadrangles along Virginia and West Virginia border (Box 502)
  - Maitland Mine, profiles 1-3 of track sections, including diagrammatic representation of minerals, no mine workings, 1975/03/28 (Box 503)
  - Maps showing coal elevation around the Guyandotte River and Pinnacle Creek -Kepler ISO maps, coal elevation, seam elevation, depth of cover, etc. (Box 503)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co., New River Division, map showing facilities to serve the Kepler mine (Box 503)
  - Profiles and map of No. 2 seam near Shumate Drift, No. 4 Seam, and other seams [unidentified mines] (Box 503)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. map showing Indian Creek, Beech Fork No. 1, Johnny Branch, No. 31 Station, and Amonate Tipple at the McDowell Co., West Virginia, and Tazewell Co., Virginia border (Box 504)
  - 2 unidentified maps (Box 504)
  - Dean seam outcrop (Box 504)
  - Bishop mine map showing train roads and topographics from end of tipple bridge, 1963/11/09 (Box 505)
  - Norfolk and Western right of way, alongside Big Branch Creek (Box 505)
  - Unknown Seam Outcrop Boundary (Box 506)
  - Map showing seam outcrops - multiple and coal Elevations around 77000 N / 37000 E (Box 506)
  - No mine workings, topographic map of Lynco Slurry Impound, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 506)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture and Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station map of Virginia, color coded soil types (Box 506)
  - Profile of Guyandotte Valley, Itmann Profile, lease line entry #1 (Box 506)
  - #10 seam, and 10 seam split (Box 506)
  - Unmarked maps (Box 506)
  - Drawings of Conventional Coal firing, coal slurry firing (Box 507)
  - Bishop/Consol Virginia, Tazewell County, topographic map (Box 507)
  - Data sheets (Box 507)
  - OSM #700542 duplicates 1-5 (Box 507)
  - Old Turkey Gap topographic map (Box 508)
  - Maps with no mine workings near Sugar Run Branch (Box 508)
  - topographic map of Consol lands (Box 508)
  - Map showing gas well locations (Box 508)
  - Cross section across upheaval top, Horsepen Mountain (Box 508)
  - OSM #700235, New River and Pocahontas Consolidated Coal Co., Beckley Seam Outcrop, Rift, West Virginia (Box 509)
  - Pocahontas Coal Company, Jenkins Jones #7, data sheets and maps of railways for mine (Box 509)
  - OSM #700183 duplicates, Peerless Coal and Coke Co., Vivian, West Virginia, area near tipple - proposed dump relocation (Box 509)
  - Consolidation Coal Co. Three Forks and unidentified topographic maps, 1981/03/31 (Box 510)
  - Test Holes in Lowes Mountain Lease (Box 510)
  - Whitesville A&S Coal Co. Inc., map showing stripping operations on property of Pocahontas land operation (Box 510)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., sugar run mines locations, surface features (Box 511)
  - Cross sections/sediment profiles of different seams on property of Faraday Coal and Coke Co. (Box 511)
  - Maps showing lands of New River and Pocahontas Consolidated Coal Co. Berwind Division, West Virginia/Virginia (Box 511)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. land (Box 511)
  - Map showing coal company properties and seam outcrops, Berwind (Box 511)
  - Air Shaft diagrams and slope profiles for Cabin Creek no. 4 and 3 seams (Box 511)
  - American Coal Co., stripping proposal, 1950 (Box 512)
  - Map of Mahan-Moore Cheeley Coal Property, Anderson & Scott counties, Tennessee, Tennessee Mining and Manufacturing Co., 1933/07 (Box 512)
  - Photographs of Itmann area/mine by Guyandotte River aerial photo (Box 512)
  - Bishop Coal Co., Upper Horsepen seam, McDowell, West Virginia and Tazewell, Virginia border, no mine workings (Box 512)
  - Tennessee topographic maps (Box 513)
  - Keppler Mine conveyor Schematic (Box 513)
  - Area near Guyandotte River and Itmann Coal Co. property, West Virginia, lease properties, outcrops, elevations (Box 513)
  - Consol prospects in Johnson Co., KY (Box 513)
  - Huntsville Surface resource (Box 514)
  - Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co., Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., McDowell County (Box 514)
  - Consolidation Coal resource analysis (Box 514)
  - Amonate preparation plant, plan view, pond profiles (Box 514)
  - Stratigraphic Profile, Pocahontas No. 5 Seam (Box 515)
  - Amonate rotary dump, Road - hand drawn and data sheets (Box 515)
  - Data sheets, corresponding with OSM #700392 (Box 515)
  - Map showing prospecting on Horsepen Creek (Box 515)
  - Data/info corresponding to OSM #700363-700366 (Box 515)
  - Data sheet for map OSM #700318 (Box 515)
  - Maps of boreholes and net tons of coal at Wyoming County, West Virginia, Ritter and Cabin Creeks (Box 516)
  - Bowman Town, West of Horsepen Office (Box 516)
  - Waterline - Dry Fork (Box 516)
  - Pocahontas Corp mine plans, building plans, accident reports (Box 516)
  - Wyoming/Mercer counties, West Virginia, topographic maps (Box 517)
  - Surface building plans (Box 517)
  - Unknown stratigraphic profile (Box 517)
  - Jacobs Creek profile, sewer and ponds of Bishop (Box 517)
  - Itmann #3 map showing outcrops of different seams (Box 518)
  - No mine workings, Amonate Property, West Virginia (Box 518)
  - Timber and coal lands, Lexington, KY area (Box 518)
  - topographic maps, 18,000 N, 11,000 E (about in the middle) (Box 518)
  - Drill hole data, no mine workings (Box 518)
  - #3 mine, Itmann side track, datasheet (Box 520)
  - Faraday Shaft site, cross sections, etc. (Box 520)
  - Satellite photo, no known location (Box 520)
  - Jenkinjones-Bishop & USS Corp. Exchange parcel boundaries (Box 521)
  - Maitland contour map (Box 521)
  - topographic maps within Kentucky showing different areas/places in Kentucky (Box 521)
  - Unknown topographic maps, Match #2, Match #1 (Box 522)
  - Data sheets for Horsepen area (Box 522)
  - Redbird purchase unite, Kentucky (Box 522)
  - Right of way and track map, the Virginia Railway Company (Box 522)
  - Consol's Faraday property showing the upper seaboard seam, Pocahontas, Virginia (Box 523)
  - Various maps detailing Rowland reserve data, no mine workings (Box 523)
  - Map showing borehole locations and holdings outlined on quads, no mine workings (Box 523)
  - Building plans, Itmann car dump (Box 524)
  - Middle Creek Area, No. 11 seam (Box 524)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Bishop preparation plant, Schematic diagram of thickener circuit (Box 524)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., building plans for Maitland mines (Box 525)
  - Prospect - Rosedale Lease, Anderson County, TN, Test holes (Box 525)
  - Lands of Pocahontas Land Corporation included in leasehold of Turkey Gap Coal and Coke (Box 526)
  - Itmann Aerial Photo, no mine workings (Box 526)
  - H&P Coal Company, No. 3 mine proposal, McDowell County, West Virginia, Pocahontas No. 9 Seam, no mine workings, 1976/11/12 (Box 527)
  - Area showing Lick Branch area, approx. locations of mines 1 & 2 in Area B, no mine workings (Box 527)
  - Consolidation Coal Co., Amonate mine plans, no mine workings (Box 527)
  - Map showing towns / quads / rivers and boundary / borders of counties and states, Kentucky / Illinois border (Box 527)
  - Lands of Mary Vizard Kelly in Harlan, Leslie, Letcher, and Perry counties, Kentucky (Box 527)
  - Building plans, Platnik's Adapter (Box 528)